<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ghost on Home Hub</title>
    
    
    
    <link>https://homehub.tech/tags/ghost/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ghost on Home Hub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Home Hub</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 19:55:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://homehub.tech/tags/ghost/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading Ghost 1.xx to Ghost 2.xx using Docker</title>
      <link>https://homehub.tech/upgrading-ghost-1-xx-to-ghost-2-xx-using-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 19:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homehub.tech/upgrading-ghost-1-xx-to-ghost-2-xx-using-docker/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Checking my Ghost installation recently and I noticed i was way out of date and needed to updated to the latest version of Ghost ( currently 2.11.1 ). Now usually this would have been the case of simply following the upgrade instructions provided by Ghost but because I am running Docker the upgrade process was slightly different.
 Before upgrading to 2.xx you will have to be on version 1.25.6 as this has the latest database changes that are compatible with the latest version.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker, Nginx and Let&#39;s Encrypt</title>
      <link>https://homehub.tech/docker-nginx-and-lets-encrypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 19:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homehub.tech/docker-nginx-and-lets-encrypt/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          In my previous blog post I explained how quick and easy it was to get a Ghost blog up and running using docker. The next step is to set up a reverse proxy and an SSL certificate. I will be using Nginx as the reverse proxy and Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt as my SSL certificate provider. All with the help of Docker!
The Container There are many Docker containers available, some official and others provided by the community.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Ghost on Docker in 2018</title>
      <link>https://homehub.tech/installing-ghost-on-docker-in-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 17:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homehub.tech/installing-ghost-on-docker-in-2018/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          I have been looking for a way to get a blog up and running in quick and simple manner. No installing and configuring databases. No installing and configuring web servers. Minimal user interaction when installing and setting up.
This is where Docker comes in to play.
Docker Minimal user interaction and you are using docker? yes i am. Using Docker will only require me to install Docker and use docker run .
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>